<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>随笔 on 羽扇纶巾</title>
        <link>https://kofi.us.kg/categories/%E9%9A%8F%E7%AC%94/</link>
        <description>Recent content in 随笔 on 羽扇纶巾</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>zh-cn</language>
        <copyright>羽扇纶巾</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kofi.us.kg/categories/%E9%9A%8F%E7%AC%94/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>当OCLP崩溃的时候的处理</title>
        <link>https://kofi.us.kg/p/1920/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://kofi.us.kg/p/1920/</guid>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;mount -uw &amp;ldquo;/Volumes/Sonoma 1&amp;rdquo; bless &amp;ndash;mount &amp;ldquo;/Volumes/Sonoma 1&amp;rdquo; -bootefi &amp;ndash;last-sealed-snapshot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>我就是测试为啥不能自动推送了</title>
        <link>https://kofi.us.kg/p/1050/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://kofi.us.kg/p/1050/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;这是用来测试自动的推送的blog&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>高考满分英语作文范文（通用25篇）</title>
        <link>https://kofi.us.kg/p/2146/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://kofi.us.kg/p/2146/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;高考满分英语作文范文（通用25篇）&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　2024年高考语文作文试题共6道。即：全国甲卷、新课标I卷、新课标II卷，以及北京卷、天津卷、上海卷。下面是小编帮大家整理的高考满分英语作文范文，希望能够帮助到大家。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://p.9136.com/00/l/lm626.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;高考满分英语作文范文（通用25篇）&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-1&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 1
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　&lt;strong&gt;新课标Ⅰ卷&lt;/strong&gt;/Ⅱ卷****&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　假设你是李华，你的美术老师带你去公园上了一节美术课，请你写一封信给Chris，要帮他介绍给外国朋友去公园上了美术课之后完成的作品和感想。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　注意:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　1.写作词数应为 80个左右:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　2.请按如下格式在答题卡的相应位置作答。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear Chris,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Im writing to share my experience of an art class in a park last Friday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　In this art class, I completed a landscape painting. The teacher told us that we didnt need complex colors and lines, and we just enjoyed it. So, I used bright colors to draw a deep blue sky and colorful flowers,completing a very healing painting for me. Although I didnt learn many painting techniques in this class, it made me realize the meaning of art.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Thank you for patiently listening to my sharing. Looking forward to your reply!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Yours sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　LiHua&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;亲爱的克里斯,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我写信是为了分享我上周五在公园上美术课的经历。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　在这节美术课上，我完成了一幅风景画。老师告诉我们，我们不需要复杂的颜色和线条，我们只是享受它。于是，我用鲜艳的色彩画出了深蓝色的天空和五颜六色的&amp;rsquo;花朵，完成了一幅对我来说非常治愈的画。虽然在这堂课上我没有学到很多绘画技巧，但它让我意识到艺术的意义。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　谢谢你耐心听我的分享。期待您的回复!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　你的真诚,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　李华&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-2&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 2
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　&lt;strong&gt;全国甲卷&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　根据给出的三张图片(shared bikes/ high-speed train/ new energy cars)，就Development of Transport in China, 写一篇发言稿。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　注意：1. 词数 100 左右；&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　2. 可以适当增加细节，以使行文连贯。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Im here today to talk about the development of transport in China, focusing on three major aspects: shared bikes, high-speed trains, and new energy cars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Firstly, shared bikes have revolutionized urban commuting, providing a convenient and environmentally friendly option for short trips. Secondly, Chinas high-speed train network has connected cities and regions, significantly reducing travel time and boosting economic development. Lastly, the widespread adoption of new energy cars has helped to reduce air pollution and promote sustainable transportation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　These advancements reflect Chinas commitment to building a greener, more efficient transport system. Thank you for your attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　今天，我想谈谈中国交通的发展，主要从共享单车、高铁和新能源汽车三个方面来谈。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　首先，共享单车彻底改变了城市通勤，为短途旅行提供了方便和环保的.选择。其次，中国的高铁网络连接了城市和地区，大大缩短了旅行时间，促进了经济发展。最后，新能源汽车的广泛采用有助于减少空气污染，促进可持续交通。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　这些进步反映了中国致力于建设一个更环保、更高效的交通系统。谢谢您的关注。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-3&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 3
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　&lt;strong&gt;北京卷&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　假设你是红星中学高三学生李华。你的外国好友Jimm准备给其校报的 Asia Today 栏目投稿。得知今年新中国成立 75周年，他打算重点介绍中国的发展成就，发来邮件询问你的建议。请你用英文给他回复，&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　内容包括:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　1.建议投稿内容;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　2.就以上建议简要说明理由。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　注意:1.词数 100 左右;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　2.开头和结尾已给出，不计入总词数。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　参考范文&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear Jim,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Its great to hear that youre planning to contribute to the Asia Today column for your school newspaper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Regarding your focus on Chinas 75th anniversary, I suggest highlighting Chinas remarkable development achievements. This could include its economic growth, technological advancements, poverty alleviation efforts, and global contributions. These topics not only showcase Chinas progress but also its impact on the world stage, fostering a deeper understanding of Chinas role in global affairs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　By emphasizing these achievements, your article can provide valuable insights into Chinas journey over the past 75 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Yours,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Li Hua&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;亲爱的吉姆,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　很高兴听到你打算为校报的`《今日亚洲》专栏撰稿。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　关于你关注中国成立75周年，我建议你强调中国取得的巨大发展成就。这可能包括中国的经济增长、技术进步、扶贫努力和全球贡献。这些话题不仅展示了中国的进步，也展示了中国在世界舞台上的影响，加深了对中国在全球事务中的作用的理解。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　通过强调这些成就，你的文章可以对中国过去75年的历程提供宝贵的见解。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　你的,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　李华&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-4&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 4
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　&lt;strong&gt;天津卷&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　假设你是晨光中学的学生李津，学校即将举办”低碳校园，从我做起”英语主题演讲活动，你要参加，请根据下面提示，写一篇演讲稿。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　内容包括:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　(1)指出校园中不符合低碳环保理念的现象；&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　(2)建议从身边的小事做起，如&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　(3)号召大家采取行动。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　低碳校园 low carbon campus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　注意:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　(1)词数不少于100;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　(2)可适当加入细节，使内容充实、行文连贯;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　(3)开头已给出，不计入总词数。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　参考范文&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear teachers and fellow students,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Im excited to share with you my thoughts on creating a low carbon campus. First of all, we must acknowledge that our school still has many areas that do not align with the low carbon environmental concept. For example, unnecessary waste of paper, misuse of electricity, and the neglect of recycling bins are all common occurrences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　To make a positive change, we should start with small actions around us. For instance, we can reduce paper waste by using both sides of the paper when taking notes, turning off lights and electrical appliances when they are not needed, and actively participating in recycling programs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　I encourage everyone to take action and join hands to make our campus a greener and more sustainable place. Lets all play our part in building a low carbon campus, starting from ourselves. Thank you！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;亲爱的老师、同学们:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我很高兴与大家分享我对创建低碳校园的看法。首先，我们必须承认，我们学校还有很多地方不符合低碳环保理念。例如，不必要的浪费纸张，滥用电力，以及忽视回收箱都是常见的现象。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　为了做出积极的改变，我们应该从身边的小事开始。例如，我们可以减少纸张的`浪费，在做笔记时使用纸张的两面，在不需要的时候关掉灯和电器，积极参与回收计划。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我鼓励大家行动起来，携手共建一个更环保、更可持续发展的校园。让我们从自己做起，为建设低碳校园尽一份力。谢谢你！&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-5&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 5
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　&lt;strong&gt;上海卷&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　你是明启中学的高三学生李明，你们学校英语报开设了一个“排忧解难”专栏，你的校友Lynn发出求助，请根据她的来信写封回信：写作要求：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　提出你的建议；&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　说明你的理由。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　参考范文：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear Lynn,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　I understand your situation. Here are a few suggestions to help change your parents minds about cooking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Firstly, explain to your parents why you want to cook. Tell them its a valuable life skill and a way to relieve stress. Showing responsibility and maturity can help.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Secondly, offer to start with simple and safe recipes. Assure them you will take all necessary safety precautions and clean up afterward. You could even ask them to cook with you initially.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Lastly, highlight the benefits of home-cooked meals, like healthier eating and saving money. Mention how cooking together can be a fun family activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　By communicating openly and showing responsibility, you can help your parents feel more comfortable with the idea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Best regards,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Li Ming&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;亲爱的琳,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我理解你的处境。这里有一些建议，可以帮助你改变父母对烹饪的看法。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　首先，向你的&amp;rsquo;父母解释你为什么想做饭。告诉他们这是一项宝贵的生活技能，也是一种缓解压力的方法。表现出责任感和成熟会有所帮助。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　其次，提供简单安全的食谱。向他们保证你会采取一切必要的安全预防措施，并在事后进行清理。你甚至可以让他们一开始和你一起做饭。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　最后，强调家常菜的好处，比如更健康的饮食和省钱。提到一起做饭是一项有趣的家庭活动。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　通过开诚布公的交流和表现出责任感，你可以让你的父母对这个想法感到更舒服。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　最好的问候,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　李明&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-6&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 6
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　In the picture,we can see a boy in worn clothes,sitting at a shabby wooden table with a pile of books on it.A weak ray of light came in through a small hole in the wall and he was absorbed in his reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　This is a well-known story from an ancient Chinese idiom.The boy,being poor,ccfflldnt afford even a candle,so he bored a hole in the wall to &amp;ldquo;steal&amp;rdquo; light from his neighbors house to read at night.The moral of the story is: spare no effort to acquire knowledge and never get discouraged easily no matter how difficult the situation may be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Of course,things are totally different today.It is not the story itself but what is reflected in the story that counts.Hard work pays off.We should take pains to improve ourselves through learning and get prepared for the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　在这幅画中，我们可以看到一个男孩穿着破旧的衣服，坐在一张破旧的木桌上，上面放着一堆书。一缕微弱的光线从墙上的一个小洞射进来，他全神贯注地看书。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　这是一个著名的中国成语故事。这个男孩很穷，连一支蜡烛都买不起，于是他在墙上钻了一个洞，“偷”了邻居家的灯，晚上读书。这个故事的&amp;rsquo;寓意是:不遗余力地获取知识，无论情况多么困难都不要轻易气馁。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　当然，今天的情况完全不同了。重要的不是故事本身，而是故事所反映的内容。努力工作会有回报的。我们应该努力通过学习来提高自己，为未来做好准备。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-7&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 7
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　The mouse is a most effective device used by people to communicate with a computer.For most people,its almost impossible to operate a computer without a mouse,let alone surf the Internet.A well-chosen mouse is really handy,flexible and convenient in controlling the screen.With the functions of ing,deleting,moving and copying,it enables us to edit test,browse web page and download what we want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　It can even bring us a flood of music,movies and PC games.Just imagine,all this can be done with a cute mouse.A convenient tool can certainly make our work easier,but it doesnt always help in a positive way.Too much ready information on our fingertips leaves little room for knowledge pursuing.Too many ready answers make us less excited in finding truth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Relying too much on mouse clicking makes us lazier and less creative both mentally and physically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　鼠标是人们用来与电脑交流的最有效的工具。对大多数人来说，没有鼠标操作电脑几乎是不可能的，更不用说上网了。一个精心挑选的.鼠标在控制屏幕时确实很方便、灵活和方便。它具有删除、移动、复制等功能，使我们能够编辑测试，浏览网页，下载我们想要的东西。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　它甚至可以给我们带来大量的音乐、电影和电脑游戏。想象一下，这一切都可以用一只可爱的老鼠来完成。一个方便的工具当然可以使我们的工作更容易，但它并不总是以积极的方式起作用。太多现成的信息在我们的指尖留下知识追求的空间很小。太多现成的答案使我们在寻找真理时缺乏激情。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　过度依赖鼠标点击会让我们变得更懒，在精神上和身体上都缺乏创造力。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-8&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 8
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　Thomas Edison Born in America,Thomas Edison was a great scientist and inventor.He was once thought to be a boy who was not worth educating.In fact,he was a man full of imagination.I admire Edison a lot because of his great contribution to the world.He had more than 1,000 inventions.In his lifetime,he was always eager to know how things worked,which helped him to earn the nickname“the Wizard of Melo Park”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　He was also so diligent that he worked day and night.And this explained why he had so many great inventions.What impresses me most is his famous saying,“Genius is one percent inspiration and ninety-nine percent perspiration.”Probably I cannot be an Edison myself,but I can be a hard-working learner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　From him,I realize the secret to success is not when or where you were born,but what you are doing and how you do it in your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　托马斯·爱迪生出生于美国，是一位伟大的科学家和发明家。他一度被认为是一个不值得教育的男孩。事实上，他是一个充满想象力的人。我很钦佩爱迪生，因为他对世界的巨大贡献。他有1000多项发明。在他的一生中，他总是渴望知道事情是如何运作的，这帮助他赢得了“甜瓜公园巫师”的`绰号。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　他也很勤奋，他日夜工作。这就解释了为什么他有这么多伟大的发明。给我印象最深的是他的名言:“天才是百分之一的灵感加上百分之九十九的汗水。”也许我自己不能成为爱迪生，但我可以成为一个努力学习的人。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　从他身上，我意识到成功的秘诀不在于你出生在何时何地，而在于你在做什么，以及你在生活中如何去做。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-9&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 9
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　My dream house is a villa which lies on the coast.There are two yards in the villa.The front yard is a garden with many beautiful flowers an plants for the four seasons.There is a swimming pool in the back yard,as my family are fond of swimming.On the first floor,there is a big hall when you enter the gate.On the right of the hall is a sitting room,there we can relax,have a rest,watch TV and enjoy entertainments.On the left there is a computer room and a study belonging to me.On the second floor,there are six bedrooms with bathrooms.The villa will be equipped with the modern equipment,such as security alarms controlled by computers,vision phones,lifts an automatic doors.Well,that is my dream house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我梦想中的房子是建在海边的一幢别墅。有两个别墅庭院。前院是一个有很多美丽的花的植物在四个季节的花园。后院有一个游泳池，因为我的家人喜欢游泳。在一楼，有一个大厅，当你进入大门。在大厅的&amp;rsquo;右边是客厅，在那里我们可以放松，休息，看电视，享受娱乐。在左边有一个电脑室和一个属于我的书房。在二楼，有六间卧室和浴室。别墅配有现代化设备，如电脑控制的安全报警器，可视电话，电梯和自动门。嗯，那是我梦想中的房子。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-10&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 10
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　Air is all around us.Its around us as we walk and play.From the time we were born,air was around us on every side.When we sit down,it is around us.We live in air.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　All living things need air.Living things cant live without air.We can go without food or water for a few days but we cant live for more than a few minutes without air.We take in air.When we are working or running,we need more air.When we are asleep,we need less air.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　We live in air,but we can not see it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　We can only feel it.We can feel it when it is moving.Moving air is called wind.How can you make air move? Here is one way.Hold an open book in your hands in front of you.Close it quickly.What can you feel? What you feel is the air.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　空气包围着我们，当我们走路和玩耍的时候，它在我们周围。从我们诞生之日起，空气就在我们周围了。当我们坐下时，它在我们身边。我们生活在空气中。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　所有生物都需要空气，没有空气生物就不能生存。没有水和食物，我们可以生存几天，但是没有空气几分钟我们都无法生存。我们吸进空气。当我们工作或跑步时，需要较多空气。当我们睡着时，需要的空气会少一些。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我们生活在空气中，但我们看不见它。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-11&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 11
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　Ways of making friends Everyone needs friends,so how to make true friends is very important to anybody.First of all,you must be friendly to others.Smile at others and you always sure to get a smile in return.You should think more of others than of yourself and try your best to make a stranger fell at home.Think as you are in his position.Try to remember others names,which will make them fell that they have made an impression on you.If you dont agree with others,dont argue but discuss with them.Finally,dont believe those who leave their friends when they are in trouble because “A friend in need is a friend indeed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　交友的方式，每个人都需要朋友，所以如何结交真正的朋友对任何人都很重要。首先，你必须对别人友好。对别人微笑，你一定会得到微笑的回报。你应该多想想别人的想法，努力去做一个陌生人在家里。认为你在他的位置。试着记住别人的名字，这会让他们觉得他们给你留下了一个印象。如果你不同意别人的话，不要和他们讨论。最后，不要相信那些在遇到困难时就离开他们的朋友的`人，因为“患难的朋友才是真正的朋友”。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-12&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 12
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　I will never forget the people who have helped me, the one I will never forget is my junior high school English teacher, Linda. She speaks beautiful English and she is very friendly and friendly. She helps me a lot in my English study. She always encourages us to practice more. We often get the work right, group work, discussions and reports. She also brought us a lot of very good English songs and ballads. We never find learning English boring. As a result, I have made great progress in English. Whats more, I really enjoy learning English. I will never forget Linda who helped me in my English study. I will try my best to help others, just like Linda.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我永远不会忘记曾经帮助过我的人，我永远不会忘记的是我的`初中英语老师，琳达。她说漂亮的英语，她非常友好和友好。在我的英语学习中，她帮助了我很多。她总是鼓励我们多练习。我们经常做对工作，小组工作，讨论和报告。她也给我们带来了很多非常好的英文歌曲和歌谣。我们从来没觉得学英语很无聊。结果，我在英语上取得了很大进步。更甚的是，我真的很喜欢学习英语。我永远不会忘记在我的英语学习上帮助过我的琳达，我会尽我所能地帮助别人，就像琳达。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-13&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 13
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　As we all know,there are three stages in studypreview,study in class and review,among whichreview is the most important.From my experience,Id like to talk about the importance andsteps of review.Firstly,make a review plan with certain contents of subjects at acertain time.Secondly,carry on the review plan regularly.Thirdly,examine what has been reviewed andmake supplement in time.One thing to remember is to keep notes all the time.I follow myreview plan strictly and have made progress in my study.It turns out to be good enough.Ofcourse,there is more than one way to review.So long as we review regularly,we can find moreways to improve our studies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我们都知道，学习有三个环节：预习、课堂学习和复习，三者中复习是最重要的。我愿意从我的经验谈复习的重要性和步骤方法。首先，制定复习计划，确定在某段时间里复习课程的具体内容。其次，有规律地执行复习计划。第三，检测所复习的.内容，及时弥补。有一件事必须记住，就是要时时记笔记。我严格遵循复习计划，在学习上取得了进步，证明复习是可取的。当然，不只有一种复习办法。只要我们有规律地复习，我们可以找到更多改善学习的方法。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-14&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 14
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　Recently,we have made a survey of the people on physical training.Only 35 percent of the people surveyed have taken part in physical activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Over half of the people say they haven’t got enough time to take exercises.34.9 percent of them complain they don’t have places where they can relax themselves and that there are not enough training facilities,while another 12.9 percent of the people feel that they live too far away from the training centers.Some of them even don’t know how to train.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　For lack of physical training,many people are not in good health.People should realize the importance of it,and measures should be taken to provide people with training facilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　最近，我们提出了对体育锻炼的人的调查。只有35的受访民众曾经参与体育活动的`一部分。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　超过半数的人说，他们已经没有足够的时间采取演习。其中百分之34.9抱怨他们没有地方可以放松自己，并没有足够的训练设施，而另一百分之12.9的人认为他们生活太远的训练中心。他们中有些人甚至不知道如何培养。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　对于缺乏体育锻炼，许多人并不健康状况良好。人们应该意识到它的重要性，并应采取措施，以提供训练设施的人。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-15&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 15
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　Yesterday,I broke a vase.This vase has been in myhome for several years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　昨天，我打碎了一个花瓶。那个花瓶在我们家很多年了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　I was afraid of being criticized.I didnt dare to tellmy parents.So I pretended nothing happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我怕被骂所以不敢告诉我父母。所以我就假装什么都没发生。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　But they discovered at last.It was strange that myfather didnt blame me,but teach me a lesson.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　但是最后他们还是发现了。很奇怪我爸爸不仅没有责怪我，反而给我上了一课。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　He made me know that responsibility was necessary for everyone in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　他让我知道责任感对我这个世界上的每一个人都是必须的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　If a person was not responsible,he couldnt do anything successful and may not be popularamong the people around you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　如果一个人没有责任感，他很难取得成功，也可能会让你在你周围不怎么受欢迎。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　A responsible person would have the courage to undertake everything.This was what a boyshould have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　一个有责任感的&amp;rsquo;人会有勇气承担一切。这也是一个男孩所必须的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　If I have done something wrong,I should take the responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　如果我做错了，我就该负起这个责任。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-16&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 16
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　When you look around,you will find that the spring is coming.The breeze is gently brushing your face.The blue sky is above you.After raining,the flowers are blooming in the garden.The living beings start to grow.Everything is full with vigor and fragrance.The best season of this year,you cann’t miss it and you will love it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　The spring is coming,it brings green to the trees and grass,pink and yellow to the flowers.Activeness to the animals.Hopes to the human beings.The birds start to sing,the farmers begin to plant crops in the fields.In spring,everywhere is full of hope.People usually say that a good beginning is half done,while spring is the beginning of a year.So we should appreciate it and make the most use of it.Try the best to spread seeds in spring and you will get a good harvest in autumn.Then you will see how important spring is and how lovely it is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　当你环顾四周，你会发现春天来了。微风轻轻拂过你的脸。蓝天在你的头顶。雨过后，花园里的花盛开了。生物开始生长。一切都充满了活力和芬芳。今年最好的季节，你不能错过它，你会爱上它的。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　春天来了，它给树和草带来了绿色，给花带来了粉红色和黄色。对动物的积极性。对人类的希望。鸟儿开始唱歌，农民们开始在地里种庄稼。春天，到处都充满了希望。人们常说良好的.开端是成功的一半，而春天是一年的开始。所以我们应该感激它，并充分利用它。春天尽量播种，秋天就会有好收成。然后你就会看到春天是多么的重要，多么的可爱。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-17&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 17
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　Chinese students celebrate their birthdays in different ways.But the most common way is to have fun by drinking,singing and dancing.On the birthday,one usually receives nice gifts and good wishes from friends and parents.Sometimes,parents will prepare a special dinner or a cake to show their love for their children.Since birthday celebration is one of the important activities in ones life.It can be done in more meaningful ways.For example,we can buy some flowers or cook a delicious meal for our mothers on that day.In this way,we express thanks to our parents in return for their love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　中国的学生用不同的方式来庆祝他们的生日。但最常见的方式是通过饮酒、唱歌和跳舞来取乐。一个人在他生日那天通常会收到许多朋友和父母送给他的礼物和祝福。有时，父母们也会准备一个非常特殊的晚餐或一块蛋糕来表达他们对孩子的爱。既然庆祝生日是人一生中最重要的`活动之一，那么可以用其他更有意义的方式来庆祝。例如，在那天，我们可以亲自为我们的妈妈买一些花或做一顿丰盛的饭菜，用这种方式来回报父母对我们深深的爱。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-18&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 18
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　As we all can see,the lovely students in the picture are so active that they all put their hands high,hoping to express their own opinions.It is obvious that the atmosphere is relaxing and everyone enjoys it.Thats great,isnt it? The picture also reminds me of the time when I was a fresh student who was too shy to speak in public.Just like me,during my class,our classmates just listened to class,and everyone was watching me! I even prayed that my name would never come to my teachers mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　But as time goes by,I grow up,so as my mind.I realized that the situation show in the picture was far better.Children are all curious about everything,and knowledge will only be acquired by an inquiring mind.Those who dare not to speak out will never know anything new.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　The childhood without asking is not a real childhood.We should also keep the curiosity now,and forever.That will benefit you in the rest of your life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　正如我们所看到的，图片中可爱的学生是如此的活跃，他们都把他们的手高举，希望表达自己的意见。很明显，气氛很轻松，每个人都很享受。太棒了，不是吗?这张照片也让我想起了我还是一名新生的时候，当时我太害羞了，不敢在公共场合说话。就像我一样，在我上课的时候，我们的同学只是听讲，每个人都在看我!我甚至祈祷我的名字永远不要出现在老师的&amp;rsquo;脑海里。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　但随着时间的流逝，我长大了，我的思想也长大了。我意识到图片中显示的情况要好得多。孩子们对一切都很好奇，只有好奇的头脑才能获得知识。不敢说出来的人，永远不会知道新事物。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　没有询问的童年不是真正的童年。我们也应该永远保持好奇心。这将使你的余生受益。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-19&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 19
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　My grandfather is in his seventies now.He is a kind and warm-hearted old man.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　He used to live with my family.At that time he always spent more than one hour examining my homework every day.When I was ill,he took good care of me.He showed great concern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Grandfather is very warm-hearted to his neighbors and is always ready to help them.One day,a girl who is one of his neighbors injured her leg carelessly.My grandfather took her to the hospital at once and paid the fees with his own savings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Now my grandfather is living in another city with my aunt.My parents and I all miss him very much.And I hope that I can go to visit him soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我姥爷70多岁了，他是一位和蔼、热心的老人。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　他过去和我们一起住。那段日子里，他每天都花一个多小时的时间检查我的`功课。在我生病时，细心照料我。他非常疼爱我。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　姥爷对邻居们也很热心，总是乐于助人。一天，邻居家的女孩不慎摔伤了腿，姥爷马上带她到医院去，并用自己的积蓄帮她支付药费。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　现在姥爷和我阿姨一起住在另一个城市。我和爸爸妈妈都很想他。我希望不久就能见到他。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-20&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 20
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　I often imagine what my life will be like in the future. I think my life will be very different in ten years. Ill be 28 by then. Ill have a family of my own and maybe a lovely child. I hope to work as a programmer in a computer company. I will enjoy my job and get along well with my colleagues. Whatever I do, I will do well. In my free time, I will continue to exercise regularly, such as swimming, running and various ball games. In my holiday, I will travel around the world. In a word, my life will be more colorful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我经常想象我未来的生活会是什么样子。我认为十年后我的生活会很不一样。到那时我就28岁了。我将有自己的家庭，可能还有一个可爱的孩子。我希望在一家电脑公司做程序设计师。我会喜欢我的工作，并与同事相处融洽。无论我做什么，我都会做好的。在我的&amp;rsquo;空闲时间，我将继续定期锻炼，如游泳，跑步和各种球类运动。在我的假期里，我将环游世界。总之，我的生活会更加丰富多彩。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-21&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 21
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　I think smiling has a lot of benefits. It can not only make us happy, but also make others happy. If we smile at life, life will smile back at us. So I want to smile, whenever and wherever, first of all, I want to smile at my parents, because they give me life and take the trouble to bring me up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　They arranged almost everything for me. With their help, I have made great progress. I want to say &amp;ldquo;thank you&amp;rdquo; to them with a smile. Then my smile should be given to myself, because only in this way can I gain more confidence to smile my troubles and live a better life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　In a word, lets greet every day with a smile. Tomorrow is another day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我想微笑微笑有很多好处。它不仅能使我们快乐，也能使别人高兴。如果我们对生活微笑，生活也会对我们微笑。所以我想要微笑，无论何时何地，首先，我想对我的父母微笑，因为他们给了我生命，不厌其烦地把我带大。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　他们几乎为我安排好了一切。在他们的帮助下，我取得了很大的进步。我想用微笑对他们说“谢谢”。然后我的微笑应该给自己，因为只有这样我才能获得更多的信心微笑我的烦恼，过上更好的`生活。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　总之，让我们用微笑迎接每一天。明天又是新的一天。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-22&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 22
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　Every year,my school holds sports meeting in aboutOctober,I am very exciting about it,I can watch thewonderful game and dont have class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　My schools sports meeting lasts three days,the classis suspended,all the students go to the play groundto watch the game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　As an audience,I am so nervous and yell out &amp;ldquo;come on&amp;rdquo; to my classmate,watching they get tothe final line,I am so proud of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　The part I like most is relay race,that is so exciting,all the students yell loudly,the athleteschase one by one,nobody can be sure who is the champion until the last minute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Sports meeting bring me so many beautiful memories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　每年，我的学校大约在十月举行运动会，我对此很兴奋，我可以看精彩的比赛而不用上课。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我们学校的运动会持续三天，停课，所有的学生都去操场看比赛。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　作为一名观众，我很紧张，向我的同学大喊“加油”，看着他们走到最后，我为他们感到骄傲。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我最喜欢的&amp;rsquo;部分是接力赛，那是如此令人兴奋，所有的学生大声喊叫，运动员一个接一个地追逐，没有人能确定谁是冠军，直到最后一分钟。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　运动会带给我许多美好的回忆。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-23&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 23
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　Recently,we have made a survey of the people on physical training.Only 35 percent of the people surveyed have taken part in physical activities.Over half of the people say they havent got enough time to take exercises.34.9 percent of them complain they dont have places where they can relax themselves and that there are not enough training facilities,while another 12.9 percent of the people feel that they live too far away from the training centers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Some of them even dont know how to train.For lack of physical training,many people are not in good health.People should realize the importance of it,and measures should be taken to provide people with training facilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　最近，我们对人们的体育锻炼情况进行了调查。只有35%的受访者参加过体育活动。超过一半的人说他们没有足够的时间锻炼。34.9%的人抱怨没有地方可以放松自己，也没有足够的训练设施，而另外12.9%的`人觉得他们住得离训练中心太远了。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　他们中的一些人甚至不知道如何训练。由于缺乏体育锻炼，许多人身体不好。人们应该意识到它的重要性，并采取措施为人们提供培训设施。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-24&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 24
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　Planning Is Good ,But Doing Is Better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　Planning is good as it decides in detail how we do.However,a plan can bear no fruit without being actually carried out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　My experience in the English speech contest last October is a case in point.A month before the event,I spent hours working out a schedule outlining my goals and practical steps.After that,I set out to read widely for an inspiring topic,wrote a speech,and practiced its delivery in beautiful pronunciation with good public speech skills.I finally came out of the contest as the first prize winner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　I know how I achieved my success.It came from good planning and better doing combined.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　计划是好的，但行动更好。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　计划是好的，因为它决定了我们如何做的细节。然而，没有实际执行的计划是不会有结果的`。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我去年十月参加英语演讲比赛的经历就是一个很好的例子。在活动前一个月，我花了几个小时制定了一个时间表，列出了我的目标和实际步骤。在那之后，我开始广泛阅读一个鼓舞人心的话题，写了一篇演讲稿，并练习了优美的发音和良好的公共演讲技巧。我终于在比赛中获得了第一名。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　我知道我是如何取得成功的。它来自于良好的计划和更好的行动。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;高考满分英语作文-25&#34;&gt;　　高考满分英语作文 25
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;　　Tomatoes look like apples and they are as big as apples.When tomatoes are ripe,they are red or yellow.If you touch them they feel smooth and soft.The ripe tomatoes taste sweet and sour.In summer,you can buy tomatoes everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　People like,to cook tomatoes with eggs.You can also just cut tomatoes imo pieces and mix them with sugar.How delicious they are! But remember not to eat too much.In winter,tomatoes are fewer,but you can still buy them on the market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　西红柿看起来像苹果，它们和苹果一样大。西红柿成熟时，它们是红色或黄色的。如果你触摸它们，它们会感觉光滑柔软。成熟的西红柿尝起来又甜又酸。夏天，到处都能买到西红柿。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;　　人们喜欢用鸡蛋煮西红柿。你也可以把西红柿切成块，然后和糖混合。多好吃啊!但是记住不要吃太多。在冬天，西红柿比较少，但你仍然可以在市场上买到它们。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>青年如钢，责任如火</title>
        <link>https://kofi.us.kg/p/2211/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://kofi.us.kg/p/2211/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;钢铁在烈火中锻造，青年在责任中成长。当历史的车轮滚滚向前，当时代的浪潮汹涌澎湃，我们这一代青年站在了历史与未来的交汇点上。面对&amp;quot;青年一代有理想、有本领、有担当，国家就有前途，民族就有希望&amp;quot;的时代召唤，我们必须思考：何为青年之责任？如何在担当中成就自我，在奋斗中书写青春？&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;青年的责任，首先是对自我的责任——在理想与现实的张力中锤炼品格。诚然，理想的丰满与现实的骨感常常让我们感到困顿。但正如鲁迅先生所言：&amp;ldquo;愿中国青年都摆脱冷气，只是向上走，不必听自暴自弃者流的话。&amp;ldquo;理想从来不是空中楼阁，而是需要在现实的土壤中生根发芽。袁隆平院士年轻时怀着&amp;quot;让所有人远离饥饿&amp;quot;的理想，却要面对无数次实验失败的现实打击，但他在田间地头的每一次弯腰，都是理想照进现实的具体实践。我们这一代青年，应当学会在理想与现实的辩证统一中寻找前进的方向，在追求梦想的过程中锤炼意志品格。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;青年的责任，更是对社会的责任——在个人追求与集体利益的统一中实现价值。个人的小我与时代的大我从来不是对立的关系，而是相互成就的有机整体。当我们谈论&amp;quot;佛系&amp;quot;&amp;ldquo;躺平&amp;quot;时，不应忘记&amp;quot;苟利国家生死以，岂因祸福避趋之&amp;quot;的传统情怀。新时代的青年科学家颜宁，放弃普林斯顿大学的优渥条件回国任教，将个人的学术追求与国家的科研需要紧密结合；无数&amp;quot;95后&amp;quot;&amp;ldquo;00后&amp;quot;医护人员在疫情面前主动请缨，将青春的热血洒在抗疫一线。他们用实际行动诠释了什么叫&amp;quot;青年兴则国家兴，青年强则国家强&amp;rdquo;。我们应当明白，真正的个人价值实现，必然与社会的进步发展同频共振。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;青年的责任，还体现在面对挫折时的坚韧不拔——在困境中锻造心理韧性。人生不如意事十有八九，青年时期更是充满了不确定性和挑战性。但正如孟子所说：&amp;ldquo;天将降大任于斯人也，必先苦其心志，劳其筋骨。&amp;ldquo;挫折从来不是青年前进路上的绊脚石，而是通向成功的垫脚石。马云三次高考才考上大学，求职屡遭拒绝，但他在每一次挫折中汲取力量，最终创造了阿里巴巴的商业奇迹。当代青年面对&amp;quot;内卷&amp;quot;&amp;ldquo;焦虑&amp;quot;等现实困境时，更应该培养&amp;quot;山重水复疑无路，柳暗花明又一村&amp;quot;的坚韧品格，在挫折中成长，在困境中蜕变。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;历史的接力棒已经传到我们手中，新时代青年的责任担当不是抽象的口号，而是具体的行动。无论是在人工智能、生物技术等前沿科技领域攻坚克难，还是在乡村振兴、生态保护等国家战略中贡献力量；无论是在日常学习工作中精益求精，还是在社会实践中传递正能量，我们都应该以&amp;quot;功成不必在我，功成必定有我&amp;quot;的胸怀，在各自的人生道路上书写青春华章。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;青年如钢，需要责任之火的淬炼。让我们在理想与现实的统一中坚定方向，在个人与社会的融合中实现价值，在挫折与成长的循环中锤炼品格。唯有如此，我们才能不负时代重托，不辱青春使命，在新时代的伟大征程中绽放属于青年的光芒。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;正如习近平总书记所说：&amp;ldquo;青年是标志时代的最灵敏的晴雨表，时代的责任赋予青年，时代的光荣属于青年。&amp;ldquo;让我们以青春之我，创建青春之国家，青春之民族，在担当中成长，在奋斗中闪光！&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>青年责任与担当——新时代的使命召唤</title>
        <link>https://kofi.us.kg/p/2219/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://kofi.us.kg/p/2219/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;青年兴则国家兴，青年强则国家强。&amp;ldquo;习近平总书记的这句话，如钟声般响彻在每一个新时代青年的心中。站在历史的新起点上，我们这一代青年肩负着前所未有的历史使命，承载着民族复兴的伟大梦想。责任与担当，不仅是时代赋予我们的神圣使命，更是我们青春年华中最亮丽的底色。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;新时代青年的历史使命在时代洪流中勇立潮头&#34;&gt;新时代青年的历史使命：在时代洪流中勇立潮头
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;每一代青年都有属于自己的时代印记，每一代青年都要在历史的坐标中找到自己的位置。新时代的青年，生逢盛世，也重任在肩。我们见证了中国从站起来、富起来到强起来的伟大飞跃，也将亲手书写中华民族伟大复兴的壮丽篇章。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;在科技创新的最前沿，梁文锋这样的青年科技企业家令人瞩目。这位浙江大学毕业的85后，从探索量化交易到创办幻方量化，再到成立DeepSeek进军人工智能领域，用自己的创新实践诠释了什么是科技报国。他带领团队开发的AI大模型，不仅在技术上实现突破，更以极低的成本震撼了全球AI界，展现了中国青年在科技创新领域的无穷潜力。正如他所说：&amp;ldquo;一定存在为价格建模的方法&amp;rdquo;，这种执着探索的精神，正是新时代青年应有的品格。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;在各个领域，还有无数像黄大年、王逸平这样的时代楷模，他们用生命诠释了&amp;quot;心有大我，至诚报国&amp;quot;的深刻内涵。他们的事迹告诉我们，新时代青年的历史使命，就是要在民族复兴的伟大进程中，勇做时代的弄潮儿，在服务人民、奉献祖国中实现自己的人生价值。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;个人理想与社会责任的统一在奉献中成就自我&#34;&gt;个人理想与社会责任的统一：在奉献中成就自我
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;有人说，理想很丰满，现实很骨感。但我要说，真正的理想从来不是空中楼阁，而是在社会责任的土壤中生根发芽、开花结果的。个人理想与社会责任的统一，是新时代青年必须面对的重要课题。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;梁文锋的创业历程就是个人理想与社会责任相统一的典型例子。他从一个对数学和计算机有着浓厚兴趣的青年学子，到量化投资领域的开拓者，再到人工智能领域的领军人物，每一步都体现了把个人专业追求与国家科技发展需要相结合的智慧。他创立的DeepSeek，不仅实现了个人的创业理想，更以其开源开放的理念，为全球AI发展贡献了中国智慧，展现了中国青年的大格局和大胸怀。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;时代楷模黄大年更是这方面的典型代表。他毅然放弃国外优厚待遇回到祖国，把个人的学术理想完全融入到国家的战略需要中。他常说：&amp;ldquo;只要祖国需要，我必全力以赴。&amp;ldquo;正是这种把个人理想与国家需要紧密结合的品质，让他在有限的生命中创造了无限的价值。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;这些楷模的共同点在于，他们都把个体的小我融入了祖国的大我、人民的大我之中。他们深知，个人的前途命运与国家和民族的前途命运紧密相连，只有在为国家、为人民的奋斗中，个人理想才能真正开花结果。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;面对挫折的心理韧性在磨砺中成长成熟&#34;&gt;面对挫折的心理韧性：在磨砺中成长成熟
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;青春的路上不会一帆风顺，成长的过程中必然伴随着挫折和困难。新时代的青年要有面对挫折的心理韧性，要在磨砺中成长成熟，在困难中锤炼品格。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;梁文锋的创业路程并非一帆风顺。从最初在成都尝试将AI引入各个领域但屡遭失败，到后来专注金融领域获得成功，再到进军AI大模型领域面临的技术挑战和资金压力，每一个阶段都充满了困难和挫折。但正是这些磨砺，锤炼了他坚韧不拔的品格，培养了他面对困难不退缩的勇气。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;心理韧性不是天生的，是在一次次的困难面前锻造出来的。当我们面对学业的压力时，不要退缩，要迎难而上；当我们面对就业的挑战时，不要畏惧，要勇于拼搏；当我们面对人生的低谷时，不要绝望，要坚持希望。正如那句话所说：&amp;ldquo;宝剑锋从磨砺出，梅花香自苦寒来。&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;那些时代楷模，哪一个不是在困难中成长起来的？王逸平在与病魔斗争的同时坚持科研工作，用生命诠释了什么是科学家精神；黄大年在回国初期面对的各种困难和质疑，都没有动摇他报效祖国的决心。他们用自己的经历告诉我们，困难和挫折不是成长路上的绊脚石，而是成长路上的垫脚石。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;培养心理韧性，需要我们树立正确的价值观念，明确人生的目标和方向。当我们知道自己要到哪里去的时候，路上的困难就不会让我们迷失方向。培养心理韧性，还需要我们不断提升自己的能力和素质，用知识和技能武装自己，让自己有足够的底气面对各种挑战。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;青春的责任与担当在新时代中绽放光芒&#34;&gt;青春的责任与担当：在新时代中绽放光芒
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;青年强，则国强。新时代的青年要有责任意识，要有担当精神，要在自己的岗位上发光发热，为国家和民族的发展贡献自己的力量。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;责任不分大小，担当不分轻重。无论是在校园里刻苦学习，还是在工作岗位上兢兢业业；无论是在科研一线攻克难关，还是在基层一线服务群众，每一个青年都可以在自己的位置上承担起应有的责任。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;新时代为青年施展才华、竞展风采提供了广阔舞台。我们生活在一个伟大的时代，这个时代既为我们提供了前所未有的机遇，也对我们提出了更高的要求。从梁文锋在AI领域的开拓创新，到各行各业时代楷模的先进事迹，都在告诉我们：新时代的青年要敢于有梦、勇于追梦、勤于圆梦。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我们要珍惜这个时代，感恩这个时代，在这个时代中书写属于我们这一代人的青春华章。我们要以那些时代楷模为榜样，学习他们的精神品质，传承他们的责任担当。我们要像梁文锋一样，在科技创新的道路上勇于探索；要像黄大年一样，把个人理想与祖国需要紧密结合；要像王逸平一样，在困难面前永不言弃。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;青春是用来奋斗的，不是用来虚度的。让我们在新时代的征程上，以青春之我，为祖国建设贡献力量；以青春之我，为民族复兴添砖加瓦。让青春在新时代的广阔天地中绽放光芒，让责任和担当成为我们青春年华中最亮丽的底色。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;时代的接力棒传递到我们手中，我们要跑好这一棒，不负时代，不负青春，不负梦想。在实现中华民族伟大复兴的历史进程中，我们每一个青年都要勇敢地担当起历史责任，用青春的力量书写时代的华章，用责任的担当点亮未来的希望。正如习近平总书记所说：&amp;ldquo;新时代中国青年要树立远大理想，要热爱伟大祖国，要担当时代责任，要勇于砥砺奋斗，要练就过硬本领，要锤炼品德修为。&amp;ldquo;让我们以此为指引，在新时代的征程上勇敢前行，用青春和汗水谱写无愧于时代的壮丽篇章。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>准备弄个公众号</title>
        <link>https://kofi.us.kg/p/1540/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://kofi.us.kg/p/1540/</guid>
        <description>&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;忽然想弄个公众号, 发点东西,主要是想通过公众号阅读赚个盒饭啥的, 这不是ds 很火吗, 我主要想能不能全自动化了, 就去注册. 这一注册不要紧, 发现我这些年就帮别人注册了, 说我微信号绑定了5个公众号, 不能再绑定了,我用微信号一查询,还真是, 三个管理员, 2个长期运营者. 三个我是管理员的账号有的主体都不知道是谁了, 有的好几年都不更新, 我赶紧联系,注销.

先需要找回, 然后才能注销, 又咔咔一顿找回,然后注销, 提交了需要7天的冻结期,还有的需要审核. 还真不容易.还有一个找不到主体了, 实验了几个都不对, 不知道应该咋办了.

现在剩下的就是等待了,注销完了, 我弄个自己的, 但是写啥还没想好. &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>如何利用cherry studio 来直接使用deepseek R1</title>
        <link>https://kofi.us.kg/p/1240/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://kofi.us.kg/p/1240/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;先注册硅基流动, 然后使用 [cherry studio] (&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://cherry-ai.com/download&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://cherry-ai.com/download&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br&gt;
, 在右下角设置, 选择硅基流动, 默认里面是没有R1的, 需要手动添加的, 拖到最下面, 添加模型, 回到硅基流动的模型广场,点开R1, 显示了R1 的详细信息, 在名称后面有个复制的符号, 复制后,黏贴到cherry studio, 下面的都自动了. 现在就可以回到对话页面进行对话了. 赠送金额也可以使用.
[注册链接] (&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://cloud.siliconflow.cn/i/OXCBS3N3&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://cloud.siliconflow.cn/i/OXCBS3N3&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>逐步摸索hugo</title>
        <link>https://kofi.us.kg/p/2216/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://kofi.us.kg/p/2216/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;已经在博客的样式上摸索了好几天, 大概有点感知了,
正在逐步更新&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
